<posts>
<post>

<id>1</id>
<pagelink>post.html</pagelink>
<image>http://wallpapercave.com/wp/1fZCder.jpg</image>
<title>  I do believe every human has a finite number of heartbeats. I don't intend to waste any of mine.
</title>
<postImage>https://newevolutiondesigns.com/images/freebies/cool-wallpaper-8.jpg</postImage>
<metainfo>Posted by Alex on  March 29, 2017</metainfo>
<article><![CDATA[
 	<p>Never in all their history have men been able truly to conceive of the world as one: a single sphere, a globe, having the qualities of a globe, a round earth in which all the directions eventually meet, in which there is no center because every point, or none, is center — an equal earth which all men occupy as equals. The airman's earth, if free men make it, will be truly round: a globe in practice, not in theory.</p>
    <p>Science cuts two ways, of course; its products can be used for both good and evil. But there's no turning back from science. The early warnings about technological dangers also come from science.</p>
    <p>What was most significant about the lunar voyage was not that man set foot on the Moon but that they set eye on the earth.</p>
    <p>A Chinese tale tells of some men sent to harm a young girl who, upon seeing her beauty, become her protectors rather than her violators. That's how I felt seeing the Earth for the first time. I could not help but love and cherish her.</p>
                   
                    <p>For those who have seen the Earth from space, and for the hundreds and perhaps thousands more who will, the experience most certainly changes your perspective. The things that we share in our world are far more valuable than those which divide us.</p>

                    <h2 class="section-heading">The Final Frontier</h2>

                    <p>There can be no thought of finishing for ‘aiming for the stars.’ Both figuratively and literally, it is a task to occupy the generations. And no matter how much progress one makes, there is always the thrill of just beginning.</p>

                    <p>There can be no thought of finishing for ‘aiming for the stars.’ Both figuratively and literally, it is a task to occupy the generations. And no matter how much progress one makes, there is always the thrill of just beginning.</p>

                    <blockquote>The dreams of yesterday are the hopes of today and the reality of tomorrow. Science has not yet mastered prophecy. We predict too much for the next year and yet far too little for the next ten.</blockquote>

                    <p>Spaceflights cannot be stopped. This is not the work of any one man or even a group of men. It is a historical process which mankind is carrying out in accordance with the natural laws of human development.</p>

                    <h2 class="section-heading">Reaching for the Stars</h2>

                    <p>As we got further and further away, it [the Earth] diminished in size. Finally it shrank to the size of a marble, the most beautiful you can imagine. That beautiful, warm, living object looked so fragile, so delicate, that if you touched it with a finger it would crumble and fall apart. Seeing this has to change a man.</p>

                    <a href="#">
                        <img class="img-responsive" src="img/post-sample-image.jpg" alt="">
                    </a>
                    <span class="caption text-muted">To go places and do things that have never been done before – that’s what living is all about.</span>

                    <p>Space, the final frontier. These are the voyages of the Starship Enterprise. Its five-year mission: to explore strange new worlds, to seek out new life and new civilizations, to boldly go where no man has gone before.</p>

                    <p>As I stand out here in the wonders of the unknown at Hadley, I sort of realize there’s a fundamental truth to our nature, Man must explore, and this is exploration at its greatest.</p>

                    <p>Placeholder text by <a href="http://spaceipsum.com/">Space Ipsum</a>. Photographs by <a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/nasacommons/">NASA on The Commons</a>.</p>
	]]></article>
</post>

<post>
<id>2</id>
<pagelink>post.html</pagelink>
<image>https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1250/1*mAhSCm4jxwEL2YRmo0S9ig.jpeg</image>
<title> Hard Work is The Single Greatest Competitive Advantage
</title>
<postImage>https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1250/1*mAhSCm4jxwEL2YRmo0S9ig.jpeg</postImage>
<metainfo>Posted by Alex on March 23, 2017</metainfo>
<article><![CDATA[
 	<p>Nobody is great without work. Hard work is always the baseline of great achievements. Nothing spectacular comes without it. Getting organised is hard work. Setting goals, making plans to achieve them, and staying on track is hard work.Very few have ever failed with the hard work approach to making it in life. You may rise slowly, but you are sure to rise.</p>
 	<blockquote>There’s only one way to the top: Hard Work
	</blockquote>
    <p>There are no shortcuts to lasting success, only smartcuts. Many people will do what’s easiest and avoid hard work — and that’s precisely why you should do the opposite. Lasting success can only be achieved if you put in the work. Jim Rohn says “Don’t wish it were easier. Wish you were better.”</p>


    <p>What was most significant about the lunar voyage was not that man set foot on the Moon but that they set eye on the earth.</p>
    <p>A Chinese tale tells of some men sent to harm a young girl who, upon seeing her beauty, become her protectors rather than her violators. That's how I felt seeing the Earth for the first time. I could not help but love and cherish her.</p>
                   
                    <p>For those who have seen the Earth from space, and for the hundreds and perhaps thousands more who will, the experience most certainly changes your perspective. The things that we share in our world are far more valuable than those which divide us.</p>

                    <h2 class="section-heading">There’s no substitute for hard work</h2>

                    <p>“Don’t ever, ever, believe anyone who tells you that you can just get by, by doing the easiest thing possible. Because there’s always somebody behind you who really wants to do what you’re doing. And they’re going to work harder than you if you’re not working hard.” — Maria Bartiromo</p>

                    <p>Greatness isn’t handed to anyone; it requires a lot of hard work. The best people in any field are those who devote the most hours to their crafts.</p>

                   

                    <p>Winston Churchill, one of the 20th century’s greatest orators, practiced his speeches compulsively. Vladimir Horowitz supposedly said, “If I don’t practice for a day, I know it. If I don’t practice for two days, my wife knows it.</p>

                    <h2 class="section-heading">One last thing…</h2>

                    <p>Get over the initial hurdle by making that hurdle as low as possible, and then keep clearing really easy hurdles until you’re an unstoppable force of nature. That’s one way to approach putting in the hours to work on your life’s work.
The importance of hard work is a timeless truth. Rather than fight it, run with it and you will never be disappointed. Your life will reach a whole new level when you stop avoiding and fearing hard work and simply surrender to it.
Greatness and extraordinary success isn’t reserved for a preordained few. It is available to you and to everyone. If you are willing to put in the work, your efforts will pay off.</p>

                    <a href="#">
                        <img class="img-responsive" src="http://sujanpatel.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/hard-work.jpg" alt="">
                    </a>
                    <span class="caption text-muted">To go places and do things that have never been done before – that’s what living is all about.</span>

                    <p>Space, the final frontier. These are the voyages of the Starship Enterprise. Its five-year mission: to explore strange new worlds, to seek out new life and new civilizations, to boldly go where no man has gone before.</p>

                    <p>As I stand out here in the wonders of the unknown at Hadley, I sort of realize there’s a fundamental truth to our nature, Man must explore, and this is exploration at its greatest.</p>

	]]></article>
</post>

<post>
<id>3</id>
<pagelink>post.html</pagelink>
<image>http://www.theoutlookforsomeday.net/gallery/albums/2015/winning-films/the-outlook-for-someday-2015-the-future-is-in-your-hands-2.jpg</image>
<title> The future of the open internet — and our way of life — is in your hands
</title>
<postImage>https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2000/1*qqUzr_C06yElbc1NfiqBpA.jpeg</postImage>
<metainfo>Posted by Alex on March 22, 2017</metainfo>
<article><![CDATA[
 	<p>There are a lot of scary things happening these days, but here’s what keeps me up late at night. A handful of corporations are turning our open internet into this:</p>
    <p>What was most significant about the lunar voyage was not that man set foot on the Moon but that they set eye on the earth.</p>
 	 <a href="#">
                        <img class="img-responsive" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*ickvszselsWAGDvfIYYvww.png" alt="">
    </a>
    <pThese corporations want to lock down the internet and give us access to nothing more than a few walled gardens. They want to burn down the Library of Alexandria and replace it with a magazine rack.
Why? Because they’ll make more money that way.
This may sound like a conspiracy theory, but this process is moving forward at an alarming rate.</p>
                    <h2 class="section-heading">History is repeating itself.</h2>

                   
                    <p>So far, the story of the internet has followed the same tragic narrative that’s befallen other information technologies over the past 160 years: the telegram, the telephone, cinema, radio, television.</p>

        			<p>Each of these had roughly the same story arc:</p>
        			<p>1. Inventors discovered the technology.</p>
    				<p>2. Hobbyists pioneered the applications of that technology, and popularized it.</p>
    				<p>3. Corporations took notice. They commercialized the technology, refined it, and scaled it.</p>

                    <h2 class="section-heading">What is the open internet?</h2>

                    <p>There’s only one word to describe the open internet: chaos.
The open internet is a cacophony of 3 billion voices screaming over one another. It’s a dusty, sprawling bazaar. And it’s messy. But it has produced some of the greatest art and industry of our time.
The open internet is a Miltonian marketplace of ideas, guided by a Smithian invisible hand of free-market capitalism.
The open internet is distributed. It’s owned in part by everyone and in whole by no one. It exists largely outside of the boundaries of governments. And it’s this way by design.</p>

				<div class="embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9">
				    <iframe class="embed-responsive-item" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/qfLlBsaoweQ"></iframe>
				</div>

                <p>Only we, the public, can end The Cycle of closed systems. Only we can save the open internet.</p>

           
	]]></article>
</post>

<post>
<id>4</id>	
<pagelink>post.html</pagelink>
<image>http://wallpapercave.com/wp/1fZCder.jpg</image>
<title>  I4 believe every human has a finite number of heartbeats. I don't intend to waste any of mine.
</title>
<metainfo>Posted by Alex on March 21, 2017</metainfo>
</post>

<post>
<id>5</id>
<pagelink>post.html</pagelink>
<image>http://wallpapercave.com/wp/1fZCder.jpg</image>
<title>  I5 page 3 believe every human has a finite number of heartbeats. I don't intend to waste any of mine.
</title>
<metainfo>Posted by Alex on March 20, 2017</metainfo>
</post>

<post>
<id>6</id>	
<pagelink>post.html</pagelink>
<image>http://wallpapercave.com/wp/1fZCder.jpg</image>
<title>  I6 believe every human has a finite number of heartbeats. I don't intend to waste any of mine.
</title>
<metainfo>Posted by Alex on March 19, 2017</metainfo>
</post>

<post>
<id>7</id>
<pagelink>post.html</pagelink>
<image>http://wallpapercave.com/wp/1fZCder.jpg</image>
<title>  I7 dont believe every human has a finite number of heartbeats. I don't intend to waste any of mine.
</title>
<metainfo>Posted by Alex on March 18, 2017</metainfo>
</post>

<post>
<id>8</id>	
<pagelink>post.html</pagelink>
<image>http://wallpapercave.com/wp/1fZCder.jpg</image>
<title>  I8 believe every human has a finite number of heartbeats. I don't intend to waste any of mine.
</title>
<metainfo>Posted by Alex on March 17, 2017</metainfo>
</post>

<post>
<id>9</id>	
<pagelink>post.html</pagelink>
<image>http://wallpapercave.com/wp/1fZCder.jpg</image>
<title>  I9 believe every human has a finite number of heartbeats. I don't intend to waste any of mine.
</title>
<metainfo>Posted by Alex on March 16, 2017</metainfo>
</post>

<post>
<pagelink>post.html</pagelink>
<image>http://wallpapercave.com/wp/1fZCder.jpg</image>
<title>  I10 believe every human has a finite number of heartbeats. I don't intend to waste any of mine.
</title>
<metainfo>Posted by Alex on March 15, 2017</metainfo>
</post>

</posts>
